TicklePhysics! Woohoo!
Rania released two new silicone catsuits a while ago.
One with a D-cup and one with an H-cup.
But since not only the cups but also the sizing in general is different,
they asked me to do a comparison video.
We have a silver one, this is the D-cup.
And this is the H-cup.
It's going to be a piece of work.
I'm going to have a lot of fun squeezing into them,
So I will get started with the first one. See you in a sec. Okay, first thing here. There is a back zipper
Which in fact made dressing easier. Of course now you have this
Disruption of the smooth look with the zipper. So if you don't like that you have to stick with neck entry, but I
Thought it was a relief to have the back zip
There's also a crotch zip. So if you want to have a zipper you can write to them. They can make this happen.
I ordered a crotch zipper and they sent me this which is obviously a male crotch zipper.
So apparently I'd have to clarify that I want a women's crotch zipper because this is way too high.
But yeah I guess the main target and customer audience are men. So this is the default zipper.
the whole suit weights six kilogram and we have cotton filling here in the bust area
so if you remember the succubus suit for example that was silicon filling and if I would have
ordered that with silicon filling which is possible it would have been two and a half
kilos heavier so for my back I chose the cotton option here and as you can see they still stand
they look great I don't think that cotton is a disadvantage here I think it's at least for me and
my back pain is the better option speaking of the default option for male customers we have the I'm
going to like push it close there is an opening in the back side at the bottom I don't need this
as a woman if I don't want to do number second on a toilet so you can use your imagination. If you
want to ask about the option without the opening in the bag then please write to the customer
service as well as with any zipper specification or paint job or something else you want please
ask the customer service. I do not work there I cannot answer you these questions.
This is a customized color and if you look closely it glitters. There's glitter inside it, which I love.
So they have a lot of possibilities for colors. Customized colors, your favorite colors, I don't know, just ask them.
But I think the silver is a nice change to black or pink or red, especially with the glitter.
This is the standard size. So there's only one size and I am
173 centimeters tall I
Weighed 57 kilograms and I think this is a perfect fit for me. It feels a bit
thinner than the other suits I own which I don't see as a disadvantage again because it's
Easier to dress and it's very very stretchy as you can see here. It shouldn't be bigger for me
so I think this is like a really good fit it's not too wide it's it's really
snug I'm happy with that but I do have the second catsuit with a different bust
size and it's supposed to be a bit bigger in general so I will try that now
here we go instant breast augmentation for just a fraction of the price I feel
like a comic figure and I can't really... it's hard to clap because the poops are in the way
actually. Because it's so huge huge age cup. You get it? And it's really something
I'm not used to to be honest. This suit is seven and a half kilogram so again I
chose cotton filling here to save my back from a lot of paint and as you can
see in general this suit although it's one size again it runs larger than the
last one so I have a lot of spare material here for example it's also in
the backside noticeable so we have this 3d shape of the butt which is pretty
cool but I don't fill it out so there is loose silicon skin so to say. There's also
opening here but you could barely see it because it's literally overlapping
because it's too big. So as you noticed the suit before was a pretty good fit for me
this is too big. They are super stretchy so again this is really stretchy but
someone wrote me that he actually tear the suit apart while getting dressed and
And the thing I can say about that, please check the sizing chart.
It is very stretchy, but there is a limit to everything.
And at some point, just using force and brute violence won't get you into anything.
I mean, you can use a lot of water-based lube.
That's what I do.
So lube yourself up.
Lube the suit up.
But still, if it's too small, it's too small.
And then it will tear.
Please consult the size charts.
Please consult a customer service if you're unsure, please ask about the different sizing options
Maybe they have larger options available
Just don't force anything that's not meant to be
Because if you take care of your suit and if it's the right size
Then you will have a lot of fun with it. It will be a very long lasting outfit
it they're also jiggle physics again so when i walked down the stairs i was like
anyway this is a neck and fricassee no zipper in the back how did i get into it i have a video
on my channel showing exactly that but as i said with enough loop and it's also very very stretchy
so yes it's possible it's not even too hard on the nerve loop and a bit of practice anyway
what's happening uh i want to try something and i'm going to
put this one on top of it i just see like this part here
i already feel like pamela anderson from baywatch but i want to have a look in the mirror i didn't yet
oh my god this just looks so fake oh wow
so weird i look like you know these women who have like i don't know five boot jobs and it
gets bigger and bigger and bigger it looks like someone like this it's just so out of
proportions i don't know and especially with the shiny spandex now
which actually makes the suit um fit better because it pushes the suit closer to my body
so it doesn't feel too big anymore okay yeah it was it was a it was an experiment
i'm so sorry if you just stumbled onto my account and this is the first thing you see
that's not what i normally do in every video so maybe check out other videos
than that but I mean it's fun isn't it all right I managed to undress again it wasn't even that
easy to put that spandex bodysuit on top of it because it's not really slippery material so the
fabric actually stuck to the silicone one last thing about the sizing so with the formal catsuit
which was tighter I noticed that when I wear these tight silicone catsuits for
a long time I'm starting to feel an ache in the shoulders and when they are loose
like this one it's actually feeling more comfortable so this is just my opinion
maybe you like that really tight and closing feeling better anyway I think
this is way more comfortable though it doesn't look as good of course because it's a bit wobbly
all right let me know in the comments if you have a silicon catsuit by now
and if you used my code because I have a discount code so you can use that
if you're ordering something at huania they have also masks they have a lot of other stuff check
out their homepage I will link everything in the description text I got a faq video about
silicon catsuits, I got a dressing undressing video so there's a lot to
learn about silicon on my channel. I have also other materials like spandex, latex,
PVC and stuff like that. And yeah, I hope you enjoyed this one. Have a nice day. See you in the next video. Bye!